I can't believe that he said this on live TV.
The combined wealth, this is according to Oxfam, of the world's 85 richest people
is equal to the 3.5 billion poorest people.
It's fantastic.
And this is a great thing because it inspires everybody,
gets the motivation to look up to the 1% and say,
I want to become one of those people.
I'm going to fight hard to get up to the top.
This is fantastic news.
And of course I applaud it.
What can be wrong with this?
Really?
Yes, really.
Somebody living on a dollar a day in Africa is getting up in the morning and saying,
I'm going to be Bill Gates.
That's the motivation everybody needs.
The only thing between me and that guy is motivation.
I just need to pull up my socks.
Oh wait, I don't have socks.